{"questions":[{"question":"Types OF Reviews:","level":"1","answers":["Formal Reviews","Peer Reviews","The answers 1 & 2 are correct","There are no correct answers"],"team":"zebra","correct_ans":"2"},{"question":"A software system\u2019s architecture is the set of principal design decisions about the system","level":"1","answers":["True","False","",""],"team":"zebra","correct_ans":"1"},{"question":"Select One Type of nonfunctional requirement?","level":"2","answers":["user requirements","product requirements","Efficiency requirements ","2-3 is the tow Correct Answers"],"team":"zebra","correct_ans":"3"},{"question":"what is unit testing ?","level":"2","answers":["is running the code","is testing a method by software developers","is to debuging all the code ","is to testing all parts of a project"],"team":"zebra","correct_ans":"1"},{"question":"What is the advantages of writing unit tests?","level":"2","answers":[" Code maintainability as good unit tests enforces","Code testability","Design testability ","all the above answers is correct"],"team":"zebra","correct_ans":"3"},{"question":"which maintenance type is used to fix bugs\/vulnerabilities?","level":"2","answers":["Corrective Maintenance ","Adaptive Maintenance","Perfective Maintenance","all the above answers is correct"],"team":"zebra","correct_ans":"0"},{"question":"which of the following is an agile principle?","level":"2","answers":["Scrum","self-team organize","The answers 1 & 2 are correct","There is no correct answers"],"team":"zebra","correct_ans":"1"},{"question":"In Peer Review,the primary function is to use the skill of a group of people to:","level":"2","answers":["identify needed improvements","certify correctness","encourage uniformity & enforce subjective rules","all the above answers is correct"],"team":"zebra","correct_ans":"0"},{"question":"Requirement may range from a high-level abstract statement of a service or of a system constraint to a detailed mathematical functional specification.","level":"2","answers":["TRUE","FALSE","",""],"team":"zebra","correct_ans":"0"},{"question":"The review process in agile software development is usually? ","level":"2","answers":["Formal ","rarely use informal ","informal","we can't know"],"team":"zebra","correct_ans":"1"},{"question":"Software can be tested as :","level":"2","answers":["Black Box","White Box","The answers 1 & 2 are correct ",""],"team":"zebra","correct_ans":"2"},{"question":"WHY useing the Agile?","level":"2","answers":["Agile is a time boxed , iterative approach to software delivery that builds software incrementally from the start of the project","Quality improves because testing starts from day one.","All the above Answers is correct","NO CORRECT ANSWER"],"team":"zebra","correct_ans":"2"},{"question":"MVC is","level":"3","answers":[" a Software Architecture\u2019s Elements","a software Application Architecture","a software Architecture patterns","NO CORRECT ANSWER"],"team":"zebra","correct_ans":"2"},{"question":"skills required for corrective maintenance is: ","level":"3","answers":[" Superb diagnostic skills","Superb testing skills","Superb documentation skills","all the above answers is correct"],"team":"zebra","correct_ans":"3"}]}